KIAN'S B&B KARAOKE
- He needs to turn off the song now.
- I know.
- He has to turn it off.
- It's time.
LOOK OVER HERE
- Turn it off.
- Hey.
FRANTICALLY
- He has to turn it off.
- Right.
He's turning it off.
HE TURNS IT OFF IN TIME
- Great job!
- One more song!
- Are you ready? Do you have the ring?
- Yes.
Let's go to bed now.
All of a sudden?
So, the thing is,
this person used to be
a professional athlete.
- What?
- And they're working hard at Kian's B&B.
What's he talking about?
It's our employee Kim Yeon-koung,
and today is her birthday.
Don't.
- For real?
- No way.
- Seriously?
- Oh, my gosh.
So this is why you pushed it to midnight?
It is midnight! On the dot!
So he pushed it to midnight on purpose.
LIGHTING THE CANDLES IN THE BACK
STANDING BY
She's probably feeling shy right now.
- Don't we have to sing the song?
- Right.
The birthday song.
The song.
THEY START SIGNALING AGAIN
LOOK AT US
The song.
Sing the song.
The birthday song.
Let's sing the birthday song!
GETS THE MESSAGE
Go!
Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday to you
What on earth?
You're so tall!
Dear Kim Yeon-koung!
Put it on right for me.
- Happy birthday to you
- What's this?
- Put it on.
- I have to wear it?
- Put it on her.
- It's a kimjang vest.
- I'm feeling embarrassed.
Come on, you should've given me
something expensive then.
Let me put it on for you.
Do you even know my size?
Thank you.
- The goddess!
- It's perfect on you!
- She's a goddess!
Can we sing the birthday song
in the Indian way?
What will you do?
Please do it for us.
CELEBRATING HER BIRTHDAY
THE INDIAN WAY AS WELL
Do it while dancing.
CLOSING EYES
Thank you.
Okay, hold this for a moment.
I was wondering where you went.
- Come on.
- Seriously.
We planned to do it at midnight,
but you wanted to go to bed
at 11:00 p.m. so badly.
- Right.
- So we were torn.
You felt particularly tired today.
- And you wanted to go to bed early.
- Yeah.
After I took a shower…
- Yeah, didn't you become sleepy?
- Yeah, totally.
So since it's your birthday,
just rest until lunchtime tomorrow.
- Really?
- It's your birthday present.
Yeah.
Rest until lunchtime.
Then, can I go home tonight?
That might be a bit tough.
Just rest until lunchtime.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What am I going to do here
until then though?
Feel free to wash up or keep hanging out.
- Yeah? Okay.
- Okay.
When the TV was opening up,
Kian was in the back and about to cry.
Really?
THE BOSS WAS MOVED
BY THE KARAOKE ROOM OPENING
He was like,
"Finally, I get to show this."
That part was built last.
At first,
I thought of just letting people
use it freely, like a coin karaoke room,
and opening it on some days.
But now that we're here,
it turned into like a concert stage.
Yeah, when I got up there,
it did feel like a stage.
- It did?
- Yeah.
It did feel like a stage.
We should go to bed soon.
Lights-out in ten minutes.
- Good night.
- Have a good night.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- You too, even though it was yesterday.
- Just a day apart.
Good night.
Good night, everyone.
Thank you, Jun-ho.
Have a good night.
- Good night.
- You too.
You're sleeping there, right?
- Yes.
- I'm sleeping there too.
Nice!
Good night.
My goodness! Good night.
- It's the last night for you two.
- Yes.
- It is.
- The last night.
Yes, thank you for everything.
- Did you have fun?
- Yes, so much.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Have a good night.
- Bye. Good night.
BOSS GOES TO BED TOO
- Good night.
- I don't want to leave tomorrow.
- Me neither.
THE 4 FRESHMEN CAN'T SLEEP AND GET UP
We go home and it's over tomorrow.
- We'll come visit Gwangju.
- Sure.
I think I'll go to Seoul.
- Call me if you do.
- I will.
I'll give you a nice tour of Seoul.
Okay, thanks.
Can we follow each other on IG?
Let's do it.
- Let's all follow each other.
- Yeah.
When you first came,
you were having so much fun.
- It was hard to approach you.
- Sorry.
Really energetic, right?
Yeah, totally.
Darn it.
I wanted to appear like
a nonchalant city girl.
DAY 3
7:30 A.M.
JUN-HO GETS UP
YEON-KOUNG GETS UP
SHE STRETCHES AS SOON AS SHE GETS UP
ZUHA GETS UP TOO
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
SHE FINDS OUT HOW TO GET OUT EASILY
ON THE 3RD DAY
WHILE THE EMPLOYEES ARE UP EARLY
THE BOSS IS STILL SOUND ASLEEP
KIAN'S B&B
THE PRIEST GOES SOMEWHERE
HE OPENS A BOOK?
O Lord, save me.
Lord, come quickly and help me.
Glory to the Father, Son, and Holy Spirit.
As it was in the beginning,
is now, and ever shall be. Amen.
Your words, Lord…
Catholic clerics
are obligated to pray daily,
but I had to be considerate
of others' faiths.
So I went outside to do my duty.
Let us pray.
THE BOSS IS UP
HE FINISHES A 3-MINUTE SHOWER
FIRST CHANGE OF UNDERWEAR ON THE 3RD DAY
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
- You're sad, aren't you?
I don't want to go home.
SAD
I really want to stay.
- Where are you going?
- Well…
Back to your part-time job?
- Just until this Sunday.
- When does school start?
On March 3. Next Tuesday.
Next week… It's next week?
Yes.
After the entrance ceremony,
there's an orientation.
Your orientation will feel
similar to this.
- Really?
- Similar to this?
Yeah, it'll be like this.
I've only been here for a day,
and I already feel comfortable.
You got along well
as soon as you got here.
I'm used to being in groups.
- Right, living in dorms.
- I think it helps.
We always say
priests must know how to be on their own
and also know
how to get along in a community.
I think that's a virtue
everyone should have.
Right.
You must be ready now. Come sit.
I'm pretty much ready.
You know, we're all friends
who were born in 1989.
- You're right.
- Right.
But I'm still the youngest at my temple.
I need juniors.
I was scolded yesterday too.
Always the youngest
and always getting scolded.
But the bright side is
when I'm scolded
and corrected by my elders,
I don't become arrogant
or think I'm always right.
Are you leaving tomorrow?
Yes.
Tonight's the last night.
- We should use the jacuzzi tonight.
- Right.
Jacuzzi? We still haven't used it yet.
- You still haven't?
- Never.
I think we should.
I need to try the trampoline too.
Try it now.
But this is…
I feel like my knees might give out.
- This is quite…
- Don't say that. We're the same age.
Why would your knees give out?
No, I can't. My legs are shaking.
Nope.
You have to straighten your knees.
So this is how you do it.
This is fun.
I'm drooling.
- Jun-ho, are we leaving at 9:30 a.m.?
- Yes.
- Are you going together?
The three of us here.
- And Smita and Snehal.
- And the twins?
ZUHA PUTS ON MAKE-UP WITH THE GUESTS
You don't do shading?
We're not good at make-up.
- I contour and slim my face down.
- Me too.
I'm doing that now.
But your face is already slim enough.
9:30 A.M.
We'll get going now.
- Take care.
- We'll see you later.
See you later.
We should say goodbye
to those who are checking out then.
Right, we should.
Stay healthy and enjoy your school life.
- Okay.
- Stay healthy. I'll see you again.
- It was so fun thanks to you two.
- Likewise.
I'll never forget it.
- Let's meet again sometime.
- Sure.
- You grew close, right?
- Yes.
Take care.
- See you later.
- Have a safe trip.
JUN-HO, SANG-CHEON,
SNEHAL, SMITA, AND SEUL GO OUT
Will you be ready by 10:50 a.m.?
GETTING READY TO CHECK OUT
How do I get my luggage out?
I'll help you bring it down.
- Thank you.
- I got it.
- You can let go.
- it might spill out.
Just stuff it in even if it's full.
I'll take something out if it won't fit.
Right, toss it if it doesn't fit.
NOISY
This is crazy.
THE BOSS GOES INTO THE SAUNA?
There's no privacy.
Why am I so tired?
What's this?
- Did you sleep?
- Yeah.
I have no alone time.
How do you think karaoke was last night?
It was fun.
Was it okay?
Yeah, it was fun.
You think they found it new and fun?
Of course.
Everything must've felt new to them.
- I talked to Seul and Jun-ho earlier
- Okay.
And they wanted to try the jacuzzi.
- Really?
- Yeah.
We should use it today then.
THE BOSS'S AMBITIOUS CREATION
- We should use the jacuzzi a little.
- Yeah.
DAY 3 EVENT
JACUZZI
They're exchanging numbers.
- They're exchanging numbers now.
- Yeah?
- They're leaving soon.
- Right.
Are they checking out at 11:00 a.m.?
Yeah, out at 11:00 a.m.
Is there anything we can do for them?
Once they check out, it's all over.
You know what makes you so kindhearted?
No, what?
You keep wanting to do something for them.
Is there anything we can do?
I thought about new things to do
for guests checking out.
I wanted to communicate with the guests,
so that's what I thought about.
HOW WILL THEY DO IT?
I'm feeling hungry.
Are you eating lunch later?
Should I make something now?
- Okay.
- Hey, you want to eat too?
Sure.
- I should do it now.
- What will you make?
- I'll fry up last night's leftovers.
- Okay.
BRUNCH
FRIED RICE WITH LEFTOVERS
LEFTOVER NO. 1
COLD RICE
LEFTOVER NO. 2
CABBAGE SALAD
I guess I can put all of it in.
LEFTOVER NO. 3
PORK BELLY
THE BOSS'S CABBAGE FRIED RICE
It looks good.
- Jun-ho.
- Yes?
Today's my birthday.
- What would you like?
- What?
- What do you want for your birthday?
- Boss told me
to get some rest.
Then, rest. Don't even come up.
- Rest.
- I can't. I'm climbing up.
Gosh, I'm beat.
By the way, the way I see it,
when new guests come,
we just say, "Hello!"
- Right.
- And I think that's awkward.
- There's no introduction.
- Right.
And we came out late.
We should greet them
and introduce ourselves properly.
So I bet they felt awkward yesterday.
So, I thought we could serve
welcome drinks.
- Welcome drinks?
- Yeah.
I thought of that too yesterday.
YESTERDAY AFTERNOON
We should give them welcome drinks.
When the guests came, they didn't know
what to do either, so it was a bit…
Maybe squeeze lemon juice into some water.
- It's like a juice detox.
- It's healthy. Yeah, it's good.
It's a healthy drink.
Sounds good. Let's do that.
ZUHA COMES TO THE KITCHEN TOO
- Hello.
- Hey.
First, let's eat this.
They'll leave at 11:00 a.m.
- So, before they leave…
- Okay.
Let's go to the table outside
and ask them one by one
how they liked their stay.
You want to hear how they feel?
- For the last time?
- As a sort of goodbye?
Yeah, I want to let them pick
who they want to talk to.
GUESTS CHOOSE EMPLOYEES FOR THE CHAT
GUESTS WILL CHOOSE?
- Oh, no.
- That's cruel.
What if I don't get picked?
I'll cry.
- You never know.
- You think so?
YOU NEVER KNOW
Let's do that.
That's not bad.
This should be ready, right?
It's okay.
Everyone, come on up.
WITH GUESTS
Let's go.
We're serving you brunch. Hurry.
BRUNCH BEFORE CHECKOUT
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
Try it.
- It's good.
- It's so good.
Yeah.
You want to stay longer, don't you?
- Yes!
- Really?
I hope you made some good memories.
I'll write them in my diary.
Yeah, definitely.
My first memory as a 20-year-old.
It was great.
Before you leave, for the last time…
BEFORE WE LEAVE?
If you have an employee
you want to talk to,
you can pick one
to talk with before you go.
It's not a formal meeting.
- Just a casual talk.
- Yeah.
SURPRISED
My heart is racing.
Boss thought it'd be nice
to do this before you leave.
BOSS'S IDEA
TALKING TIME BEFORE CHECKOUT
And I'm not sure we'll have enough time.
It's our first try.
THEIR FIRST CHECKOUT SERVICE
- Then, should we do it in pairs?
- Sure.
- Do it in pairs.
- Sounds good.
All right.
- Wait.
- No, wait. Hold on.
- We can't give you much time.
- Wait. In that case…
THEY HAVE A MEETING
What do we do?
What do you mean?
- I'm so torn.
- I like Yeon-koung.
And I'm sad because I didn't get to
talk much with Jun-ho.
And with Kian and Kazuha, I didn't get to…
No, Hee-jeong. Then, that's everyone.
We have to pick one.
SHE CAN'T DECIDE
Just pick one. It's nothing serious.
Anyone you want.
I mean, we won't get hurt.
We won't. It's all right.
Okay.
HEE-JEONG AND JAE-EUN'S CHOICE
Who will it be?
- Me?
- Yes.
Gosh, I was picked!
We were going to pick her. How could you?
BITTER
- I've been so nice to you.
- But we were so torn.
No, it's really all right.
I guess it definitely wasn't Boss.
No, that's not it!
- Right?
- No! This is wrong. Wait.
This is a misunderstanding.
All right.
Who do you want?
IT'S TIME
FOR JEONG-WON AND DON-HEE TO PICK
- Don-hee. Yeah.
- Should we say it?
GETTING HIS HOPES UP
All right.
- We pick you.
- Really?
THEY PICK ZUHA
We pick you.
I've been so nice to you guys.
FLUSTERED
KNEELING
And I'm the one who suggested this!
- No, hold on!
- No!
I mean, we won't get hurt.
EMOTIONALLY DAMAGED
Go on ahead.
We better do the dishes.
We'll do the dishes in the meantime.
Let's go.
- What a special moment.
- I know.
He came out.
KIAN FOLLOWS THEM OUT?
I have to talk with him a bit.
He has to throw out the food waste.
HIM = FOOD WASTE
Don't worry about him.
Yeah, go on.
I need to have a talk with you.
I'LL TALK TO THE FOOD WASTE
How did you become food waste?
AFTER A SHORT CONVERSATION, THEY PART WAYS
I need to be really good to the guests.
This kind of hurts.
STARING
- Oh, no.
- Oh, no!
BOSS
Darn it.
HE STEPPED IN SOMETHING
The weather's nice.
Darn it, how do I open this?
Hey, Jun-ho.
- Jun-ho?
- Yes?
Sorry, but…
Seriously?
- Sorry.
- For real?
It just happened.
You want me to open the door?
I'm sorry, it's…
I'm cold.
Darn it! Put the kitchen
on the first floor next time!
There you go.
- Pull.
- One, two, three.
- Leave it like this.
- Okay.
I have to go back up.
It's tough to climb up now.
Good luck.
- Let's go in.
- It looks so nice inside.
BENCH NEXT TO SKATING RINK
OUTDOOR TENT
So you start college in March, right?
- As dance majors?
- Yes.
- Do your best with dance.
- And study hard.
- Yes.
And lose weight.
Why keep saying that?
DANCE MAJORS ALWAYS WATCH THEIR WEIGHT
Most people lose weight
like cramming for entrance exams.
- Right.
- Everyone does that.
It's like studying. You cram
and forget everything after the test.
ARTS AND SPORTS CAN RELATE
It's the same thing.
- But you always…
- Yeah?
It seems like you always
keep that balance.
Have you ever wanted to give up?
Like, "I can't do this anymore."
Many times.
You have a breakdown at times, right?
YEON-KOUNG'S WAY TO PERSEVERE
There are many different ways,
but whenever you feel like that,
you'll have people who support you.
Right.
They believed in me
and that I could succeed,
so I didn't want to let them down.
And even when I wanted to quit,
I had that sense of responsibility.
And it made me pull myself together
and keep going.
So I hope you two
will control things like that.
You're in your twenties.
So, you can build your future slowly.
I think this will stay deep
in my heart for a long time.
- I'll always remember this.
- Right, exactly.
That's good to hear.
Is there something you want to do?
- In the future?
- Yeah.
As for me, I want to become
the best in my field.
- I want to…
- You should dream big.
Yes, I want to become
the top expert in the field.
- And I want to become famous.
- Famous?
Yes, my dream is
to become famous in my field.
That's cool.
Please root for me.
Of course, I will.
If you have a goal
and imagine yourself achieving it,
isn't it quite exciting?
- Myself being successful?
- Yes, imagining it.
You can do it.
- Yes, I can do it.
- Yes, thank you.
- We had just gotten close.
- Right, so it feels sadder.
It's sad that you're leaving.
- We won't forget this.
- This was a great start to our twenties.
Boss, we're back.
- Was it a good talk?
- Yeah.
Did you have a good time?
What did they say?
When they were with us,
they were pretty different
from when they were with the others.
- I bet.
- Yeah, their energy was different.
SOMEWHAT JEALOUS
I enjoyed my time too.
It was therapeutic.
It's time to check out now.
You can write
in the visitors' log if you want.
- Let's write something.
- Okay.
WRITING IN THE VISITORS' LOG
Kian's B&B will be remembered forever.
I'll make it big and come back.
Should I write, "Let's go, 07s"?
All done.
- MAY THIS BE REMEMBERED FOREVER
- HEE-JEONG
- KIAN'S B&B'S POWER BILL IS ON ME
- JEONG-WON
SOUND OF WRITING ON PAPER
YEON-KOUNG'S PREPARING SOMETHING
TO JAE-EUN
They're nothing special. I have my books…
This is awesome.
AUTOGRAPHED BOOKS
I have stuff too.
Thank you.
ZUHA'S ALBUM
Mine are pajamas.
- One for everyone.
- Thank you.
Weren't you wearing this?
- Yes, they're the same.
- Thank you.
I should give them something too.
Goodness.
I don't have anything.
All right, kids. Have one of these.
Thank you.
Hold on.
Vegetable juice.
Thank you.
I won't drink this.
- I was so thirsty, but I won't drink it.
- Seriously.
She said, "I was so thirsty"!
Vegetable juice.
- We'll get going now.
- Thanks for coming.
Okay. I'll be rooting for you.
- Hey, all the best.
- Thank you.
Take care of yourselves.
Bye.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
SAD
- Take care!
- We wish you the best!
- Bye!
It's hard to leave.
- Why did it feel so short?
- Right?
Let's save it in our hearts.
Right. Let's take a last look and go.
It was like a house I dreamed of
when I was a kid.
We had drinks
and talked together.
I thought, "This is what being young is."
KIAN'S B&B IS ABOUT "YOUTH"
The surroundings, the house,
and the people were all so romantic.
That was a dream to me.
KIAN'S B&B IS "ROMANTIC"
Five stars.
Because imagination became reality there.
It's been fun.
- I hope you hit it big, Kian's B&B.
- I hope so too.
THE FOUR OF THEM CHECK OUT
Our first guests have left.
The empty beds feel so strange.
We have to clean those empty spaces too.
Clean the second and third floors?
We should dust the blankets off.
Jun-ho, let's dust this off.
Okay.
HUGE T-SHIRT COMFORTER
- Let's go.
- Go.
SHOUTS
Hold tighter. The edge.
We should do it ten times.
We've done five.
- Go. Six.
- One.
Two.
- Three.
Okay. Fold it like this.
- Are you good?
- Yes.
- She's good at climbing that.
- Right?
CLEANING THOROUGHLY
BOSS FOUND SOMETHING
Plastic bags…
Gosh, my arms.
Here they are.
BRINGING A PLASTIC BAG
Kian, we threw out the food waste.
And we can throw out
recyclables tomorrow, right?
Hey, there's something…
The toilet.
- The toilet? What's wrong?
- I mean…
The toilet bowl?
No. Let's empty the bathroom bin together.
- Sure.
- And we should…
put it in this.
Why? Is there a lot?
Well, I think…
AT A LOSS
Is something scary in there?
NERVOUS
Well, it is possible.
BEING VAGUE
Got it.
So let's throw this out first.
- Let's empty it in here.
- In there? Combine them?
Now, if we put them together…
It's not a lot, but…
Please.
- There won't be anything.
- That won't…
- Lift it.
- Here. Put it in.
Put it in.
Just put it in here.
Wait. Then…
I'll use this to…
- Lift it.
- I…
I've never seen…
- other people's poop before in my life.
- Really?
Hello.
IN 38 YEARS OF MY LIFE
19 YEARS SINCE MY DEBUT
- I've never seen other people's poop.
- Really?
Never?
- I mean…
- In Season 1, I saw some.
But it's weird to see it again.
PRESSING DOWN
It's been a while, so it's shocking.
THE SHOCKING THING
HE HASN'T SEEN IN A WHILE
Hey, this is…
- We should've put a bag in.
- My goodness.
- To throw it out like that?
- Yeah.
- Okay, throw it out now.
- I'll go throw it out.
HE THROWS IT OUT
Gosh, that was so funny.
HE PUTS THE BIN BACK
WITH A GARBAGE BAG INSIDE
SCRUBBING HARD
- Zuha.
- Yes?
Do you think
we should empty the bin or not?
It's not too full yet.
- Right?
- Yes.
It's best to put
a plastic bag in the bin first.
- Know what I mean?
- You're right.
- We just emptied ours.
- Hold on.
ADVICE FROM EXPERIENCE
We'll do it tomorrow.
Did we clean everything?
- I think we're all done.
- Right?
LET'S GET SOME REST
Why am I hungry?
What's for lunch today, Boss?
- Seaweed soup for you.
- Seaweed soup?
Shouldn't we have it
since it's your birthday?
Then, we should go buy some seaweed.
- I bought it.
- What?
I bought it yesterday.
You bought that?
WELL-HIDDEN SEAWEED
We hid it there
so that you wouldn't find out.
Really?
You really didn't catch on yesterday?
I didn't.
It was perfect.
Anyways, I feel embarrassed.
So you'll make seaweed soup for me?
- We will, but…
- Yeah?
I've never made it for ten people,
so I don't know how much to make.
You're going to make it?
- Yes.
- That's good.
Actually, Jun-ho,
why don't you be the main chef today?
- Seriously?
- How about that?
BOSS'S IDEA
TAKE TURNS BEING MAIN CHEF
That way, the guests can know
who's cooking and feel excited.
I'll do it tomorrow.
What do you say?
Why am I going first?
He must be feeling pressured.
Then, I think I should start cooking now.
It's going to take that long?
You're that unsure of yourself?
I need to think about the recipes.
You're going to cook for six hours?
Will I get a proper dinner?
Or should I have some snacks?
We have many snacks.
We should go to the supermarket.
Right, let's go grocery shopping.
- Dharma Teacher, I'm in your hands.
- Sure.
Let's talk casually.
THEY WERE ALL BORN IN 1998
DAEGWALLYEONG SAFARI FARM
It's so picturesque.
That horse is beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
THEY'RE HERE FOR HORSEBACK RIDING
FIRST TIME FOR THE FOUR BEGINNERS
I've ridden horses
in the country for ten years.
But I'll take it easy and ride it safely.
THE EXPERIENCED ONE GOES FIRST
Then, I'll try it first.
I guess you've wanted to run too.
It looks like a scene from a movie.
- He looks cool.
- He does.
THE BEGINNERS TRY IT TOO
The scenery is so nice.
I like this.
It's so cute to have
the dog come up with us.
I didn't know horses were so charming.
They're beautiful.
Hooray!
- This was fun.
It was so much fun.
- Have a good time!
- We'll see you later.
AFTER HORSEBACK RIDING
SKY RANCH
POTTERY CAFE
It's huge.
- The closer we get, the bigger it gets.
- It looks bigger.
NAKSANSA TEMPLE, YANGYANG
Naksansa's so big.
It's huge and beautiful.
A BEAUTIFUL TEMPLE
OVERLOOKING THE EAST SEA
Let me know if you have a question.
I'll be your guide.
I appreciate it.
If you take a look,
most temples by the sea
have statues of Guanyin
overlooking the sea.
- Guanyin overlooking the sea?
- Yes.
I'll just follow you around today.
I learned a new thing.
Temples by the sea
have Guanyin statues overlooking the sea.
GUANYIN OVERLOOKING THE SEA
Do you want to ring the bell?
I do it often at my temple.
But you…
THE PRIEST TRIES IT
Do you want to do giwabulsa?
What is that?
A RITUAL WHERE YOU WRITE
YOUR WISHES ON CLAY ROOF TILES
MAY MY WISHES COME TRUE
It means, "Seek enlightenment above
and save others below."
- "Sangubori Hahwajungsaeng"?
- Yes.
I'll write, "Love, mercy, and peace."
CAPTURING THE MOMENT
WHEN RELIGIONS UNITED
Thank you.
Thanks to you,
I'll never forget my time
at Naksansa Temple.
Now, let's buy what we need.
THE STAFF ARRIVES AT THE MARKET
We're doing welcome drinks, right?
Here. Lemon juice. Get the good ones.
- This one?
- Yeah.
Should we go back now?
Let's have some outside food this time.
- Here is your bread.
- Thank you.
It does look delicious.
HERE FOR DAEGWALLYEONG POTATO BREAD
BOSS USES HIS HANDS
The coffee makes me feel much better.
- I feel energetic now.
- Right.
Boss looks a bit listless.
- Do I?
- Yeah, don't you think so?
I'll try to dig deep.
Doesn't he look tired?
I am.
Why don't we do this today?
When we have dinner,
- we always sit in a circle.
- Right.
I don't really like that.
- Then what?
- I want us to be freer.
Do you have an alternative?
Like a hotel breakfast,
what if people get their food
and eat wherever they want?
How about that?
Right now, it feels too…
- Eat wherever they want?
- Yeah.
Right now, being in one big group
is too much.
That's my opinion. What do you think?
But I like the way it is.
- You like that?
- Yeah.
There are old guests and new ones.
Dinner's the only time
when they can all spend time together.
And that's when they can
get to know each other.
"Hello, today's my first day.
My name is so-and-so."
"Is that so? Nice to meet you."
- It's like that.
- Really?
What do you think, Zuha?
Me? Well, that's our first chance
to talk to new guests, so I liked it too.
- You liked it?
- You did? See?
Last night's karaoke too.
They talked and danced
in separate small groups.
The karaoke room.
I feel the same about that too.
What about it?
With the karaoke room,
it goes, "Okay, we're about to begin."
- And everyone looks.
- Right.
That's like a forced group activity too.
It's because there actually aren't
many things we all do together.
- So…
- There aren't?
No.
From the guests' perspective.
- Really?
- What do we do together besides dinner?
When we have drinks,
people break off into groups.
EMPLOYEES SUPPORTING GROUP
VS BOSS SUPPORTING FREEDOM
And those who want to drink join them.
Come to think of it…
Then, let's not change things.
Let's just eat in a circle today then.
All right.
And about the door.
I keep wanting to compromise.
When you went outside
to talk with them earlier,
he was doing the dishes.
Okay.
I couldn't open the door.
It's too tough.
BOSS WANTS COMPROMISE ON DOOR
But we can't keep it open.
COMPROMISE REJECTED
But we, as the staff,
come and go so often.
Still, it's a rule.
REJECTED AGAIN
I mean, let's make an exception
for the staff.
- I'll open it for you.
- What?
No, it's not like
you're there all the time.
Kazuha will open it for you.
All right. Let's do that.
- We can't lose hope and dreams.
- Right.
Guys, don't forget. Hope and dreams.
I shouldn't think this way.
You're getting a call.
Is it a guest calling?
- Hello?
Hello.
We're heading
to Kian's B&B now to check in.
How many of you are there?
Three people.
I see. Three?
Where are you?
We're in Pyeongchang right now.
Then, I'll send you the address.
Okay. Then, we'll go there right now.
WE'RE STILL OUT
No, you can't come in if you arrive now.
Can't we wait in the car?
Wait, so you have nowhere to go right now?
- No.
- Then, you should come now.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay, let's go now.
Let's get this packed to go.
RETURNING EARLY AGAIN TODAY
KIAN'S B&B ENTRANCE
It's deep in the mountains.
It's like going to a military camp.
- What is it?
- I think that's it.
The orange roof.
Yeah! It says "Kian's B&B."
ORANGE ROOF SPOTTED
It's huge.
It's like a big version
of a dog house in the countryside.
Let's unload our luggage.
Let's do that.
Who could that be?
I can't see inside.
THE STAFF ARRIVE TOO
Hello.
- They're here.
- What?
They're athletes.
You're right.
- They are.
- Really?
- Hello.
- Hello!
- We meet just as we're all here.
- Right.
It's Kim Yeon-koung. Hello.
Hello.
- Hello.
Let's go.
You're athletes, right?
- We ride sleds.
- Sleds?
This way, please.
- Go ahead.
- Be careful.
Thank you.
- Ms. Kim's so tall.
- She's really tall.
So that's why the door handle's so high.
Only she can open it.
It's bigger up close.
EVEN SHE CAN'T OPEN IT
You have to…
open this to go in.
- Try it.
- Give it a try.
I'll try.
- He opened it.
- It's open.
HE SUCCEEDS WITH ONLY ONE JUMP
- Welcome.
Welcome to Kian's B&B.
Wait…
- Let's go in. Thank you.
- Yes.
Those clothes are really huge.
Incredible.
They have a pole this time as well.
I saw the pole right away.
I thought,
"I finally get to experience this,"
and I became excited.
It felt like a giant's studio apartment.
It was exactly like
how a Kian's B&B should be.
Everything's so big.
There are rooms in the fridge.
Where?
There are rooms in here.
It's a fridge?
It's just like a house.
This is amazing.
Should I make
the welcome drinks in the paper cups?
Right away with welcome drinks?
We should taste it first though.
EYEBALLING THE RATIO
This one.
- I'll hand these out.
- Let's go.
HURRIEDLY MADE WELCOME DRINKS
Everyone.
- These are welcome drinks.
- Welcome drinks.
Here.
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Welcome.
This is our first time
giving welcome drinks.
Really?
FIRST WELCOME DRINKS
It's like lemon water.
- Juice detox.
- It's like a detox.
Healthy drinks.
SNAPPED AWAKE
How is it?
- It's good.
- Lemon water.
You're athletes,
so you watch your diet, right?
- Yes.
- We do.
Lemon water.
Anyway, welcome.
- Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
BUT WHAT SPORT DO THEY PLAY?
Sledding? Bobsleigh?
We're luge athletes.
- Luge?
- That's right.
A WHILE AGO
OLYMPIC SLIDING CENTER
LUGER LEE GI-PYO
LUGER YOUN YOUNG-HYUN
LUGER CHOI JIN-AN
We had a competition today.
- Really?
- Today?
- We did.
- We came straight from there.
So you're currently active?
We had tryouts two days ago.
NATIONAL TEAM TRYOUTS
He was selected.
And we're backups.
The next in line.
If you're backups, then…
So, there are athletes
on the national team.
And if someone gets injured,
they replace them.
- So that's how it works?
- Yeah.
Then, you must come to this area often.
- Yes, to train.
- I bet you come here a lot.
You must know this area well.
What are some good restaurants?
- But…
- The thing is,
we only go to two places.
We only go back and forth
between the center and the dorms.
IT'S THEIR FIRST TIME GOING ON A TRIP HERE
So we actually don't know
the area that well.
- You don't?
- No.
- You can unpack first then.
- Okay.
How do we get up there?
Actually, you have to
just go up by yourself.
It's so cozy here.
Since they're athletes,
they can get up easily.
What's on the second floor?
The sink is a jacuzzi.
- Jacuzzi?
- Yes.
It's like a hot spring.
And there's a skating rink outside.
And next to it,
there's a place where you can talk.
Like a campsite?
There's a place where you can rest.
- Okay.
- Got it.
- Can I sleep here?
- Sure, you can.
You're sleeping there?
- Young-hyun and I will take turns.
- Then, I'll sleep here.
JIN-AN PICKS 2ND FLOOR OF FRIDGE
In that case…
BOSS'S LUGGAGE
This luggage… Were you using this spot?
No, I wasn't. You can use it.
I CAN JUST MOVE
The karaoke room?
He's a wanderer.
It's pretty cozy.
TOOTHPASTE, LOTION, TISSUE,
BUDDHA STATUE
HIS THIRD MOVE IS DONE
Do you like bread? Have some.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
It's still warm.
- Thank you.
Sure. How old are you, by the way?
I was born in 2001.
I was born in 2002. I'm 25.
- I was born in 2003. I'm 24.
- We're the same age.
Gosh.
SHY
STARING
Kazuha?
- Are you Kazuha?
- Yes, I am.
I got it right.
- I've seen you a lot on TV.
- Really?
You do ballet.
BALLET GENIUS ZUHA
You did ballet?
I did. You didn't know?
- I didn't either.
- Really?
I did ballet for 15 years.
- Fifteen years?
- Yes.
Really?
How is that possible?
When did you start?
- When I was 3.
- When you were 3?
Can 3-year-olds do ballet?
They can with their moms' help.
That's why you're flexible.
That's amazing.
I didn't know you did ballet.
THEY'RE FINDING OUT
THE EMPLOYEES' SKILLS
There's gym stuff too.
Cycling with this view?
Who is this tall?
I used it.
I'm too short for it.
Now, it fits.
TRYING THE GYM
How do I get up there?
CLIMBING THE FRIDGE
You have to jump.
Do it in a cool way.
Like this?
I'd do it this way.
Do a dip and then use your foot?
You're different.
I'd do it this way.
He's on another level.
What I would do is…
And sleep right away.
AFTER THE CLIMBING CONTEST
CLIMBING THE POLE
How is that possible?
He's good.
HE COMES BACK DOWN
And just slowly let go.
Should we go out and see the skating rink?
CHECKING OUTSIDE WHILE THEY'RE AT IT
The door's so big.
A cow is here.
It's a real cow.
I see. That's its trough.
Want to go see it?
It's so big.
LET'S GO SEE THE COW
It wants you to pet it.
Hi, cow.
Goodness.
You're cute. You have a horn.
Bye, cow. Enjoy your food.
The skating rink.
CHECKING OUT THE RINK
"Kian's B&B Waterville."
- Winterville.
- Right, Winterville.
- Let's do our pre-meet ritual.
- Here?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come up.
Two, three.
KIAN'S B&B'S FIRST CELEBRATION
- Lu!
- Woo!
But if there's a rink,
shouldn't there be skates?
- Mr. Kian.
- Yes?
I heard you had skates?
Right. Hold on.
Aren't you tired? You had a meet today.
We are.
- But since you're here?
- Yes.
You can choose your sizes here.
SKATES
Come in.
- I'm 270 mm.
- They're the real deal.
Should I try too?
I guess I should.
"Winterville."
KIAN'S B&B WINTERVILLE
THE OPENING OF WINTERVILLE
Can we skate on it when there's no ice?
Apparently, we can
since it's made with synthetic ice.
NEW TECHNOLOGY
It feels real.
This is my first time.
This really works.
THE NEW TECHNOLOGY WORKS
I'll follow you.
TAP, TAP, TAP
WALKING?
Turn.
CLUMSY
I guess not all
winter sports athletes skate well.
I think we're similar.
No, we're not.
- I want to race.
- Shall we?
How should we do it?
"Catch the Tail"?
Create some distance.
- North, south, east, west.
- Right.
Like this?
THEY'LL MOVE IN ONE DIRECTION
TO CATCH EACH OTHER
- Okay.
- Ready, set, go.
He's fast.
RUNNING HARD
He's coming!
You're out.
HE SEES AN OPPORTUNITY
STAGGERING
AFTER TOUCHING HIM
FALLS IN BATTLE?
Mr. Kian!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I caught one.
Want to go one-on-one?
- One-on-one?
- Okay.
KIAN'S IN THE FINAL
It's all about endurance.
Are you ready?
GI-PYO VS. KIAN
Mr. Kian's form looks good.
HE ENDS UP RUNNING AGAIN
HE RUNS TOO
- It won't end.
- We should've gone to a track.
I'm so tired.
He takes the inside lane!
IN DANGER
PERSEVERING
Hold on.
WORN OUT
I'm so exhausted!
KIAN LOSES THE BATTLE OF ENDURANCE
This is tough.
I'm so tired.
MEANWHILE
They didn't finish them.
WELCOME DRINK
I should clean up.
WHILE YEON-KOUNG IS CLEANING
Need help, Jun-ho?
Maybe later.
TODAY'S MAIN CHEF, JUN-HO
The seaweed…
MAIN DISH
SEAWEED SOUP FOR YEON-KOUNG'S BIRTHDAY
SOAKING SEAWEED IN WATER
PORK?
I want to make seaweed soup with pork.
FOR THE INDIAN TWINS
STIR-FRYING PORK AND SEAWEED TOGETHER
CHECKING THE RECIPE
SEASONING GOES SMOOTHLY
CONTINUES
TO STIR-FRY
LETTING THE SOUP SIMMER NOW
ANOTHER DISH FOR TODAY
ROLLED OMELET
Are you making rice?
You have to do it for us.
BOSS'S JOB TO MAKE RICE
- I have to fry the eggs now.
- Okay.
- And I have to add some water to the soup.
- All right.
Hey, you kept everything
in a neat line.
Otherwise, I'd feel uncomfortable.
I bet you're… What were they called?
"J" types from the MBTI test?
He's totally a perfectionist.
He's so J. Look at this.
So organized.
STRIVING TO BE PERFECT
I should bring over more drinking water.
- Drinking water?
- We're almost out.
WITH THE REMAINING WATER
HE MAKES THE RICE
Mr. Kian.
Yes?
We're in trouble.
What is it?
- I was just washing my hands.
- Okay.
Is it clogged?
- In there?
- The sink.
- The sink's clogged?
- The sink?
Yes.
There's a lot of poop.
Hey, help!
Hey, why are you on all fours?
HANDS FULL OF MUD
STRAIGHT TO THE SINK
It's not washing off.
They use cow poop in fertilizer,
so it'll be okay.
HE CAUSED TROUBLE
Then…
I'll try to unclog it.
BOSS TO THE RESCUE
It's not going down.
Why won't it go down?
HUNCHED
MUDDY WATER IS GOING DOWN
WORRIED
It has always drained slowly too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So you don't have to feel so guilty.
Okay.
Is it okay now?
Hold on. I'm checking.
It seems okay.
SUCCESSFULLY UNCLOGGED
Thank you.
I think some dirt had piled up.
Is it in storage?
GOES STRAIGHT TO STORAGE AFTER
Gosh, my legs.
I'm sorry, but can you
open the door for me?
PANTING
Thank you.
I'll do it.
I wonder who will be there.
THE TWINS ARRIVE IN THE MEANTIME
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Welcome back.
Sne-mita.
Sne-mita, say hello to the new guests.
- Hello.
- What's your name?
- I'm Youn Young-hyun.
Youn Hyeong-yeon?
- Young-hyun.
As time goes on,
Mr. Kian is looking more and more tired.
- Do I look tired?
- Yes.
Compared to the first day,
you're slowly getting more…
- I'm hanging in there.
- You are?
I'm hanging in there.
Can you take this up there?
How do I send this up?
HOW DO THEY LIFT
THE WATER JUG INTO THE KITCHEN?
- I'll take it and pass it.
- In the middle?
JIN-AN TO THE RESCUE
I'll hold you. Use one hand.
With one hand?
Grab it.
Be careful.
WITH ONE ARM
IN ONE GO
WATER DELIVERY'S DONE
- Nice.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Could you fry the eggs?
Okay!
Prepping the ingredients
must've been really hard.
It didn't take long.
What kind of shape do we need to make?
No shape. Just spread it out like this.
And once it's cooked a bit,
just roll it right up.
- Like an omelet?
- Yeah.
And we just cut it later.
Then, it becomes a rolled omelet.
That's right.
YEON-KOUNG TRIES ROLLING IT FIRST
It is too big to roll.
Incredible. It looks so delicious.
It looks like a proper omelet.
ZUHA TRIES NEXT
I tried making it a rectangle.
NEAT
- How is it?
- It looks perfect.
- It came out great.
- You did well.
It's perfect.
PUTTING IT ASIDE
PLACES NEATLY
Such a perfectionist.
Look at you put the board away
neatly to the side.
What is it?
I'm too nervous to make rolled omelets.
Why would you be nervous?
Too nervous for rolled omelets?
Because he sets everything so neatly
before cooking.
I don't think I can cut this.
He's trying so hard to cut it gently.
PERFECTIONIST'S NEATLY PLATED
ROLLED OMELET
We need to let the soup boil, right?
Yes.
ADDING WATER
We have to simmer it for a long time.
LETTING IT SIMMER IS THE KEY
ADD WATER AGAIN
He cooked with care.
He put in a lot of effort.
I can see that.
Seriously, since it's your birthday,
I wanted to make good seaweed soup.
I told you it doesn't matter.
It does to me.
But still…
- Are you done?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
- There it is.
- It's open.
- Are you back, Jun-ho?
- Yes.
We unified our religions.
- Hello.
- Welcome back, Father.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
SEUL IS BACK TOO
Let's go down.
And set up the food?
YEON-KOUNG
AT THE BOTTOM
ZUHA
IN THE MIDDLE
JUN-HO
UP TOP
Careful.
3-STAGE DELIVERY
Hold the handles if you can.
- You got it?
- Let go.
- I'll let go.
- You got it?
- Just lay it out.
- Right.
- It looks nice today.
- It does.
CHEF COMES DOWN IN A COOL WAY
Thank you for cooking.
Gosh, the amount…
I hope it's enough.
Come on, hurry! It looks good!
I'm so hungry.
- I'm hungry.
- Let's eat.
Explain it to them.
Explain?
Okay. First of all…
GETTING UP
We prepared seaweed soup
and rolled omelets tonight.
Today is Yeon-koung's birthday.
TODAY'S MY BIRTHDAY
I made seaweed soup.
And since the twins can't eat beef,
I tried to make it with pork.
So detailed.
Thank you for the food.
Dig in.
- I'm nervous.
- Someone has to scoop the food first.
I haven't cooked much before,
so I'm really nervous.
Please enjoy.
- Thank you!
- Is this the pork? Is it good?
NERVOUS
Please be delicious.
Jun-ho, it's so good.
Is it okay?
BRIGHTENS UP
Jun-ho, I'm having seaweed soup
on my birthday thanks to you.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
He said he wasn't a good cook,
but it was so delicious.
I'll remember my birthday for a long time.
He was so considerate
since we don't eat beef.
I was so grateful and so moved.
It's good.
- Is it okay?
- Yes.
FEELING REWARDED
That's a relief.
We should use the jacuzzi later.
We'll open the jacuzzi later,
so use it if you want.
Or you can use the sauna.
BOTH ARE OPEN
- Shall we do the dishes?
- Sure.
We should do it quickly.
HESITANT
So, there's a suggestion
we'd like to humbly make.
The staff did all the dishes
for us yesterday.
How about we do them today?
- Yes.
- Let us do it.
DISHES?
ENDLESS DISHWASHING EVERY DAY
I think I'll definitely get
the housewife's eczema.
How about we do them today?
SMIRKS
But…
They love it.
CAN'T HIDE HER FEELINGS
Let Boss decide.
Well, they want to do it so badly.
What can we do?
NODDING TIMIDLY
It's actually a rare opportunity
to do the dishes here.
- It's decided.
- Yes.
Thank you!
I'll be upstairs,
so hand them to me one by one.
Here. But it's…
I'll do it.
- Father Andrea, are you okay?
- Yes?
- I'm fine.
- You are?
Get some rest.
- Thank you.
We're done. Let's clean up here.
- Good job.
DISHWASHING'S DONE
Gosh, it's so clean.
FILLING THE JACUZZI
BUT THE WATER PRESSURE IS TOO WEAK
I've turned it on all the way.
How is it, Boss?
I think it'll take quite a while.
We have to wait a bit.
IT'LL TAKE AN HOUR
BOSS GOES TO THE SHOWER
DIFFERENT CLOTHES?
DAY 1
DAY 2
DAY 3
THE SAME CLOTHES
HE CHANGED HIS CLOTHES ON THE 3RD DAY
Want to play a game?
What kind of game?
- Hide-and-seek?
- Or how about this?
One person covers their eyes
and goes around taking pictures.
You try to not get caught on camera.
In that case…
The one taking pictures is it.
The photo game.
BLINDFOLDED PHOTO GAME
- Want to play?
- Yes.
We're going to play a game.
WHILE WAITING FOR THE JACUZZI
- Shall we try it then?
- Yes.
First, we should pick the one
who'll take the photos.
- And cover their eyes.
- Cover their eyes?
The rest must avoid
getting caught on camera.
The one who's shown the most is it next.
And let's set the number of shots.
Three shots?
- Three?
- Yes.
Okay, three shots.
Okay, let's do it.
WARMING UP
Why are you warming up?
- You should.
- We have to warm up?
You have to flee like this.
Really?
NERVOUS FOR NO REASON
ROUND 1: SNEHAL IS IT
Pull it lower.
Give me your left hand.
- Hold on.
- He's so kind.
This is the button.
Here we go.
ROUND 1 BEGINS
SHE GOES FORWARD
STEALTHILY
SLOWLY… THEN SUDDENLY!
Geez!
- She's like an assassin.
- What's going on?
AN ASSASSIN WITH A CAMERA
PLOPS DOWN
I think she got me.
- I'm done.
- She's done.
ROUND 1 ENDS
- She's fast.
- She's good at faking.
Let's check all the photos.
This one caught nothing.
This one has nothing.
Who's this?
She got one.
It's Kazuha.
- It's Kazuha.
- No, it's not.
IT'S NOT ME
IT IS YOU
Isn't it Zuha?
SHE DENIES IT
This is her too.
ZUHA AGAIN?
ZUHA AGAIN!
- It's Zuha.
- It is.
I kind of had a feeling.
- Zuha's it.
- I'm it?
ROUND 2: ZUHA IS IT
I'll make sure to take good photos of you.
Here I go.
ROUND 2
CRAWLING
She's doing it so calmly.
VERY CALM
A LOT OF FLAILING AROUND
She's doing it so calmly.
THE BOSS IS FLAILING AROUND THE MOST
- I'm done.
- Done?
ROUND 2 ENDS
I think I got caught.
You're everywhere.
- What?
- Hey, look.
- That's not me.
- They're your feet.
- No.
- They're your pants.
- Next one.
- It's because you're tall.
- Next.
- What's that?
Zuha, you took
such a good photo of yourself.
AN UNEXPECTED MIRROR SELFIE
- Who's this?
- Hold on.
Hey, it's Yeon-koung!
It's like Attack on Titan.
It's Attack on Titan.
DEJECTED
YEON-KOUNG IS IT
You were everywhere.
- The last round.
- Okay.
Because we have to use the jacuzzi.
LAST ROUND
I know the method now.
- Okay.
SHALL I GET STARTED?
POINTING THE CAMERA TO THE FLOOR
BOSS AVOIDED THE CAMERA
BY LOWERING HIS BODY
AND YEON-KOUNG OBSERVED THIS
SHE'S GOING FOR KIAN
HE LOWERS HIS BODY AND COMES IN AGAIN
KIAN
TURNING AROUND WITH THE CAMERA
LAST ROUND ENDS
She's good.
- I'm so tired.
- She's so good.
I bet Kian was caught more than once.
CURIOUS
Who's this?
It's me.
So that's how it turned out.
He's praying.
Kian!
- Kian84!
- What?
KIAN AGAIN
You caught him so well.
All the pictures look like this.
KIAN A THIRD TIME
How do they all look the same?
All three are from the same angle.
They're the same shots
AMAZED
- You were below me, right?
- Yeah.
I only shot photos of people
moving around below me.
Click, click, click.
BLINDFOLDED PHOTO GAME COMES TO AN END
If you want to use the jacuzzi,
you can get changed and go up.
- Okay.
THE JACUZZI'S FULL NOW
Can we use the sauna too?
- Of course.
- Whatever you want.
THE JACUZZI'S FIRST GUEST IS?
YOUNGEST LUGER YOUNG-HYUN
EXHALES
Gosh, it's hot.
Goodness.
JUN-HO JOINS WITH TOWELS
How's the water up there? Is it warm?
CURIOUS
It's so good.
It's good? I should join.
It's warm? That's good.
RELIEVED
It's so warm.
It feels good.
A SUCCESSFUL OPENING FOR THE SINK JACUZZI
This is good enough.
- I said we should come here.
- Warm water's the best.
KIAN COMES INTO THE SAUNA
FOUR PEOPLE IN THE SAUNA
BOTH ARE OPEN
What made you apply for this?
I've never been
to Pyeongchang for vacation.
- You've never been on a trip here?
- No.
When we heard Kian's B&B would open here,
we decided to apply.
But do athletes like you have the time?
The season's over, so…
- It ended?
- Yes, today.
- Your last match was today?
- Today was the last competition.
CAME TO KIAN'S B&B
RIGHT AFTER SEASON'S END
So how does luge work exactly?
When you start, you begin seated.
Then, you paddle with spiked gloves on.
Like this?
Yes, you start like this,
and then you lie on your back.
What does the track look like?
From the mountain top…
- You race down the slope?
- Yes, that's right.
It's the same track for bobsleigh,
skeleton, and luge.
- The same for all three.
- Really?
All on one track.
- This might sound bad.
- Okay.
But I actually didn't know.
I've seen luge before,
but I'd never heard the name before.
We have to win medals
for it to become known.
Now that we've talked like this,
I want to see you guys
compete at the Olympics.
Seriously.
If we do, will you come?
If you really do,
I'll definitely be there.
I really hope you make it.
Want to go to the sauna?
Are there many people?
I think four people?
I think it'll be better to join them.
A LOT OF TIME PASSED WHILE THEY TALKED
It feels like it's getting cold.
Should we just go like this?
Dry off with a towel before you go down.
DRYING THEMSELVES WITH TOWELS
What's going on? It's so popular today.
The sauna's packed.
THE SAUNA'S SO POPULAR
It's overwhelmingly more popular.
It's so nice here. It smells good.
And I can sweat it out.
It's great once you get a taste.
KIAN ADDS WATER
Here it comes.
Yes, this is it.
That's what I'm talking about, Boss. Yes!
Today's been the best day at Kian's B&B.
This is it.
- Are you sweating?
- It's so nice.
I'm sweating a lot.
My pores have opened up.
I need to stay here.
Thirty more minutes.
PLANNING TO STAY 30 MINUTES MORE
Thirty minutes.
THE LIGHTS WENT OUT?
Someone turned them off.
FLUSTERED
What's going on?
- Boss.
- What's going on?
- This is scary.
- It is scary.
This is scary.
Kian's B&B is…
all about teamwork.
- Focus.
- Six, seven, eight.
Nine, ten.
Why are you flapping around so much?
Hey, this is like a communal laundry spot.
Kian's B&B is all about stamina.
Where's Boss?
My teeth are also part
of the cleaning area here.
Is that so?
Geez, you're just creating more work.
I'm exhausted.
This is suffering.
The work is endless at Kian's B&B.
- No!
- He made a big mess.
Why are you making her cry?
Get it together!
What's that?
Who is that?
- It's snowing hard.
- There was a heavy-snow alert.
Why did it snow so much?
The door wouldn't open.
Hey, the building's collapsing.
We're not stuck, right?
We're stuck.
We need to shovel the snow.
Clearing snow is our job.
Isn't the snow here clean?
They're fighting again.
Want to make a snowman?
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu